[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "And Don, what's the latest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Hey, the key word here is tonight.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Don"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "(On camera): When you look around at all this, what do you think, Evelyn?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Whew.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Evelyn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "(On camera): How did you get out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ":", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Right there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "It's one of the -- one of the most scary things I would imagine that you could ever be through, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "It was -- it was very surreal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "I mean I -- when you've seen how many people have died, it's bordering on miraculous that nobody, given where you are on the scale of this destruction did lose their lives, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "It really is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Can you tell me what's going on in relation to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1974"], "LOCATION": ["Mississippi", "Alabama"]}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "CD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "Mr. Fugate, how bad is this and certainly in comparison to tornadoes we've seen in the past?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "We are looking at the damage in Mississippi, but particularly Alabama, you have to go back to 1974 to see this bad of a tornado outbreak.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Fugate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Alabama"]}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "What is the first thing that you do as a FEMA administrator to try and get to the communities that have been most hit here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "JJS", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Well again, with this type of response, the governor of Alabama and his teams are leaving the response.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FEMA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["spring"]}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Is this a very unusual time that we are experiencing here from your experience?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "It's been a very busy spring.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "What is the first thing they should be doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "First thing is to take care of yourself and your family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["National Weather Service"], "LOCATION": ["East Coast"]}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "VBZ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Are you expecting more?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "There's a slight risk for some more tornadoes and severe weather on the East Coast, but the National Weather Service, their storm prediction center, kind of like the hurricane center for tornadoes, they were putting out forecasts several days ago of a risk of a moderate and then a high risk of tornadoes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "And it's been going great guns, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Yes, I think about 200,000 downloads, a little more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 241, "question": "What are you going to say now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Well, I'm told that at the party --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "How would you sum it up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "I think -- well, firstly, you know, as you've mentioned before, you know, two bank holidays back to back with a few days of work in between and glorious sunshine is an incredible thing in England, anyway.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJR", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "What do you think she would have made of this occasion of William's choice of bride?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "I don't think she could have been happier, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "So I think that Diana would have been really happy that he'd found somebody with a kind of strength of character to be able to deal with the things that she couldn't deal with, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "I mean you've had to deal with extraordinary media scrutiny over the years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "What advice would you give them to living in this weird goldfish bowl?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "I think always to put the public's affection above the media's need for headlines, I suppose.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJS", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VB", "POS", "VB", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Barely put a foot wrong in that time, has she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "I think she has most people's respect in a sense even if they're not royalists, I think she has the respect of -- the fact that she's gone this long, let's be honest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Why does America go so crazy for royal events like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Well, I think, probably because there isn't that much coverage of anything on international television which is really linked strongly to the past.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "When we want to get things pumping at Prince Harry's disco, which of all your songs is the one that you would absolutely say is to the banker to get things going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I'd have say \"I'm Your Man\" for that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "You think \"I'm Your Man\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "\"I'm Your Man,\" I think yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "WRB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Where are you going to watch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I'm not telling you where, but I am going to a party.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "A royal wedding party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Well, it's kind of -- I'm not sure if it's a royal wedding party or a bunch of people really taking the mick.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "What message would you give the happy couple?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "I think the one that I put in the card, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Household Cavalry"]}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "All those guys on the horses looking immaculate, they're your men, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "They're the Household Cavalry, they're only a small part of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Household Cavalry", "Household Recovery"]}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "What would you personally be doing tomorrow on the big day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "As command of the Household Cavalry, I oversea the whole of the Household Recovery, all the guys on horses going out on parade.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Do you get nervous or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "No, you train.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "So what will you be thinking about him on the day as one of your own?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "It is a huge privilege to have had him in our regiment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "You wouldn't argue with him, would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "After that, I'll be riding two inches higher in the saddle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "We still don't know who made the dress, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "What are you most excited about tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "I'm excited about the dress.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I think the Brits, we do two things better than anybody in the world, in my opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNPS", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "What does it this mean to you as a Brit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Well, I know the Americans are fascinated with it, because I just came back from Americans and everybody was talking about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Because I think that they are joining the biggest reality show on Earth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNPS", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Which one is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Well, allegedly, although I don't know, she loves \"Love Never Dies.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Do you think we're getting a good one here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I think we really have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "You wouldn't even know what Twitter is, would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Lord Sugar"]}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "It's got something to do with bird song?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "But you, Lord Sugar, have become my sworn enemy on Twitter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Lord?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I have 470,000 or something like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "What would you thoughts be for the happy couple?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Well, they've got to be happy on the day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Andrew, what would your wishes for the happy couple be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "I hope that they have real happiness and also bringing humanity to other people, and being able to do their unique situation with a bit of joy, to be able to bring something that really lifts other people out of their own condition.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Lords, your lordships -- what do I call you, your lordships?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "It's a gaggle of lords.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Can it ever be relaxing to have dinner with the queen, her majesty, the queen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Oh, I assure you, she's an amazing lady with great conversation and incredible knowledge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Any comparisons between what happened there and what's going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "EX", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "I think they're about the same size, except for more technology nowadays.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United Kingdom"]}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "What kind of man is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "I think he's a great young man and dearly loved by not only the people in the United Kingdom but the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Have you met Kate yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "Yes, we did at one of the occasions.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Is it very intimidating to come into the royal family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "It's not easy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "It's rather extraordinary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "So you're officially Serbian again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "Do they have a kind of routine, do you think, that they keep by?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "After a few years, you become sort of vaccinated, no doubt about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "Your name is Morgan Higdin (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Morgan Higdin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Can you tell me your story?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "Well, we had been watching the news, so we knew that there was a tornado coming, but we weren't sure where exactly it was going to hit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "Can you see the building?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "No, I'm on the other side.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Any kind of warning at all though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "There was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "From start to finish, how long do you think the process took?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "I think it was probably over with in 20 seconds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110428pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "That's all for us tonight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]